Anton Niel A. Mojica

Full stack web developer with over 6 years extensive experience in developing and Implementing interactive websites.

Proven ability in developing and optimizing web application with use of emerging technologies.



#3016 San Roque St. Fiesta Communities Brgy. Tabun, Angeles City 2009 Pampanga

anton.mojica@yahoo.com



0935 498 5253

anton.mojica



https://anton-mojica.github.io



Work Experience

06/2015 - Present

PHP Web Developer Shore360, Inc

Philexcel Business Park, 2F-3 Business Center 6 M.A. Roxas Highway, Clark Freeport Zone Philippines 2023

- Lead web developer for an reputable australian removalist (MiniMovers)
- Build efficient, testable, and reusable PHP modules
- Solve complex performance problems and architectural challenges
- Implementing visual elements and use in the web application
- Implement best practice coding standards(User Friendly, W3C Valid Markup)
- Optimize website for best performance(SEO Ready) Google and Yahoo standard, with grade A score.
- Producing, Managing, Modifying websites and all web application with the use of version control (git) including database
- Developing cross-browser and cross-platform compatible web application
- Web Application Test(Development -> Staging -> Production) identifying bugs technical problems. Troubleshoot, test and maintain the core product software and databases to ensure strong optimization and functionality
- Participating in discussions with clients to clarify what they want.
- Participating in discussion with the Digital Marketing Team
- Make recommendations on the use of new and emerging technologies.

05/2013 - 06/2015

Web Developer

Stall 6 Sto. Entierro cor Macapagal St. Angeles City

DTW Designs Studios

- Implementing designs to be develop into live web application for clients,
- Creating user-friendly website and CMS
- Optimizing web asset for optimal speed and performance
- Basic SEO(Image optimization, meta tags, google analytics, google webmaster)
- Providing maintenance, troubleshooting and support for client web applications/websites

02/2013 - 05/2013

Contract Web Developer

SELF-EMPLOYED - Odesk.com(upwork.com)

- PSD/AI to xHTML/CSS to Wordpress
- Delivering cross-browser W3C valid HTML/ CSS markup
- Develop Wordpress Theme
- Implementing designs to be develop into live web application for clients.
- Creating user-friendly website and CMS
- Optimizing web asset for optimal speed and performance
- Basic SEO(Image optimization, meta tags, google analytics, google webmaster)

Key & Technical Skills

Project Management, Team Management, Server Management, Time and Stress Management, Perspective, PHP, MySQL, Word-Press, Magento, HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, NodeJS, Vue.js, API, Version Control, Web Optimization

Applications Used/Know

Adobe CreativeSuite | Sublime Text | Sourcetree, MySQL Workbench | Xampp | Git | Visual Studio Code | FileZilla POSTMAN API DE

Certifications

Full-Stack Javasript MVC: Realtime Web and Mobile Apps (2017) Demonstrating and understanding the concepts of VueJS, Quasar Framework, NodeJS, Firebase and Feathers

Education

06/2008 - 2013 (under grad)

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology AMA Computer College Angeles Campus Londale Bldg. Flora Ave. Angeles City

Languages

English | Filipino | Kapampangan | Visayan

ln	16	er	6	St	5
				J	

Cars Video Games DIY's Guns EDC Sport shooting
Character Reference is available upon request.
Anton Niel A. Mojica